{"data":[{"question":"George is not enough intelligent to pass this economics class without help.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"enough intelligent","b":"to pass","c":"this","d":"economics","answer":"1","explain":" - Enough intelligent-> intelligent enough","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"25","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"There were so much people trying to leave the burning building that the police had a great deal of trouble controlling them.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"There were","b":"much","c":"the burning","d":"that","answer":"2","explain":" - Much-> many","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"25","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"John lived in New York since 1960 to 1975, but he is now living in Detroil.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"in","b":"since","c":"is now living","d":"in","answer":"2","explain":" - Since-> from","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"25","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"The fire began in the fifth floor of the hotel, but it soon spread to adjacent floors.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"in","b":"fifth","c":"of","d":"soon spread","answer":"1","explain":" - In-> at","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"25","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"Mrs. Anderson bought last week a new sports car; however, she has yet to learn how to operate the manual gearshift.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"last week a new sports car","b":"however","c":"has yet to learn","d":"how to operate","answer":"1","explain":" - Last week a new sports car-> a new sports car last week","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"25","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"She wishes that we didn't send her the candy yesterday because she's on a diet.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"didn't send","b":"her the candy","c":"because","d":"on","answer":"1","explain":" - Didn't send-> hadn't sent","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"25","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"They are planning on attending the convention next month, and so I am.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"planning on","b":"attending","c":"next","d":"so I am","answer":"4","explain":" - So I am-> so am I","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"25","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"Today was such beautiful day that I couldn't bring myself to complete all my chores.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"such beautiful","b":"myself","c":"to complete","d":"my chores","answer":"1","explain":" - Such beautifyl -> such a beautiful","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"25","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"While they were away at the beach, they allowed their neighbors use their barbecue grill.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"While","b":"were","c":"their neighbors","d":"use","answer":"4","explain":" - Use-> to use","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"25","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"The artist tried stimulate interest in painting by talking his students to the museums.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"stimulate","b":"interest in","c":"by talking","d":"to the","answer":"1","explain":" - Stimulate-> stimulating","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"25","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"}]}